(Bernadette:)Okay. Okay,
how about this?
(Bernadette:)They don't know
you're here with us,
(Bernadette:)so you hide in the closet.
When they show up,
(Bernadette:)we'll hear
whatever their dumb story is
(Bernadette:)about where they were,
we'll pretend to believe them,
(Bernadette:)and just when they think they
got away with it, you jump out.
(Penny:)Yeah, that's pretty good.
I love it!
I'll be all like, "Busted!"
And they'll be like, "What?!"
(Raj:)And then we'll all be like,
"Oh, yeah!"
Yeah, I-I get it.
(Raj:)I wouldn't make out
with me, either.
(Sheldon:)In here is every clock radio
I've ever owned.
(Sheldon:)Calculators, VHS tapes.
(Sheldon:)Yeah. Oh.
(Sheldon:)Sporting equipment.
Y-You have sporting equipment?
(Sheldon:)Well, oh, it's just a...
it's a... a golf ball
(Sheldon:)that my brother
threw at my head.
(Sheldon:)You can still
feel the dent.
(Sheldon:)It's right next to
the hockey puck dent.
(Amy:)Okay, why do you have
a bin of pinecones?
(Sheldon:)I used to collect
them as a child.